Well at a YouTube party I remember there
Pues en una fiesta YouTube me acuerdo
was like we got together like the
que había como nos juntamos como los
Spanish with the Americans to talk a
españoles con Los Americanos a hablar un
little about YouTube and such and the Americans there
poco de YouTube y tal y los americanos
was a guy who had like I know
había un tío que tenía como yo que sé
300,000 subscribers or something like that and the guy
300,000 suscriptores o algo así y el tío
had the audacity to tell us Oh this month
tuvo la audacia de decirnos Ah este mes
hasn't gone very well for me you know an American
no me ha ido muy bien sabes un americano
this month has gone a bit average for me I only
este mes me ha ido un poco regular solo
earned 200,000 bucks this month and we
he ganado 200,000 pavos este mes y nos
were all like what the hell he means he
quedamos todos en plan qué hijo de [__]
had the audacity to complain about
o sea tenía la audacia de quejarse de
earning 200,000 bucks a month you know but
ganar 200,000 pavos al mes sabes pero
because over there they're like used to
porque ahí están como acostumbrados a
earning so much that your
ganar como una barbaridad que si te
head explodes and of course when I
explota la cabeza y claro cuando lo
compared him to someone at that time who was
comparaba con alguien en esa época
also a Spanish speaker it was crazy to get
además hispano hablante [__] locura
paid one day even if it was
llegar a cobrar algún día aunque fuera
just for a month if I
solamente un mes yo con que lo cobrara
only got paid for one month in my life I wouldn't
solamente un mes en mi vida Ya no
ask for more let's see says Victor Gaines
exigiría más a ver dice Víctor gaines
keep dreaming [ __ ] Victor he's
sigue soñando [__] Víctor qu es
negative dude you would give him 100k
negativo cabrón tú le darías 100k
Treasury Javier [ __ ] he's also  true
Hacienda Javier [__] también es verdad
eh if you earn 200,000 a month it's a
eh si cobras un mes 200.000 es una
pain in the ass. Of course because at V of course of course it's
putada Claro porque al V claro claro es
a pain in the ass it's a pain in the ass. Because now the
una putada es una putada Porque ahora el
rest of the months and the rest of the months go down.
resto de meses e el resto de meses bajar